https://www.familyeldercare.org/privacy-policy/

At home with changing lives.
Programs
Austin Gay & Lesbian Senior Services (AGLSS)
Programs
Austin Gay & Lesbian Senior Services (AGLSS)
Privacy Policy
We honor the trust you place in Family Eldercare, In-Home Care and Caregiver Services, and we are committed to protecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. Our privacy policy describes the information we collect and how we use it.
We always welcome your questions and feedback. For payment and privacy related issues, please contact us at:
Family Eldercare, In-Home Care and Caregiver Services
phone: 512-483-3575
email: info@inhomefamilyeldercare.org
Information We Collect
We may collect information (including name, address, telephone number, email address, transaction information, credit card information and date of birth) when you:
Make a payment on our website
Become a member of our online Community Forum
Provide an application for employment
We maintain the data that you provide us in a secure database and with the highest regard for your privacy.
Information We Share with Others and Your Privacy Rights
We contract with IronStone Bank, Financial Services, to provide the merchant account for our credit card processing. We provide this company with only the information they need to perform their services and work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected. IronStone Bank is prohibited by contract from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Family Eldercare. Authorize.Net provides our online credit card payment processing.
(Revision August 20, 2009)
As a leading provider of payment management and risk management services to hundreds of thousands of online businesses around the world, privacy and data protection are of the utmost importance to CyberSource Corporation and its subsidiaries, including Authorize.Net LLC, CyberSource Ltd., CyberSource NI Ltd., CYBS Singapore Pte Ltd., CyberSource K.K., and other subsidiaries (collectively “CyberSource”). This Privacy Statement for CyberSource (“Privacy Statement”) details the company’s policies with respect to the handling of personally identifiable information (“Information”) submitted by the reader of this Privacy Policy (“You”) or otherwise collected by CyberSource via the company’s website or in the course of providing services to CyberSource’s customers. CyberSource will use and disclose Information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Statement.
To learn more about Authorize.net please click here.
Accepting Credit Cards
Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Discover
For Refund Inquiries, please contact us at:
Family Eldercare, In-Home Care and Caregiver Services
phone: 512-483-3575
email: info@inhomefamilyeldercare.org
To post funds from the merchant’s bank account back to the customer?s credit card account as a refund for a previous charge transaction, the merchant must submit the transaction ID of the original charge transaction against which the refund is being applied.
Please have your payment details and credit card information available to verify the transaction.
Events
March 4, 2021March 25, 2021
